{
    "subject": "resource/The_Towering_Inferno",
    "predicate": "property/cinematography",
    "object": "resource/Fred_J._Koenekamp",
    "human_readable": "The cinematography for 'The Towering Inferno' was done by Fred J. Koenekamp.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9652175307273865,
            "question": "Was Fred J. Koenekamp involved in the visual aspects of 'The Towering Inferno'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9632682204246521,
            "question": "Who was the cinematographer for 'The Towering Inferno'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.915073812007904,
            "question": "What role did Fred J. Koenekamp have in 'The Towering Inferno'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9058082699775696,
            "question": "What kind of work did Fred J. Koenekamp do on 'The Towering Inferno'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8424156904220581,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Towering Inferno'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6732214689254761,
            "question": "What film did Fred J. Koenekamp work on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6126591563224792,
            "question": "What is Fred J. Koenekamp known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5967918038368225,
            "question": "When was 'The Towering Inferno' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5785961747169495,
            "question": "Name a movie that features the work of Fred J. Koenekamp."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35005810856819153,
            "question": "List some other films by Fred J. Koenekamp."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cinematography for 'The Towering Inferno' was done by Fred J. Koenekamp.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4109_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a movie that features the work of Fred J. Koenekamp.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4109_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Towering Inferno' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4109_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Fred J. Koenekamp known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4109_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4109_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n### Explanation:\nThe provided context information clearly states that Fred J. Koenekamp, A.S.C., won an Oscar for his work on the film \"The Towering Inferno.\" This directly supports the statement that the cinematography for 'The Towering Inferno' was done by Fred J. Koenekamp."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}